sikids.com 2015-12-28

# SPORTS ILLUSTRATED KIDS Privacy Notice

  |  |  |   |    
**PRIVACY POLICY** |    
  
**Table of Contents** |    
* The Information We Collect
* How We Use and Share the Information 
* Privacy Options
* Your California Privacy Rights: Notice to California Customers
* Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors
* Cookies
* Our Commitment to Security
* How You Can Access or Correct Information
* Additional Information Regarding Children's Privacy 
* Changes to This Policy
* How to Contact Us
| 

|    
  
This is the Privacy Policy for the United States of America which applies to you if you live outside the European Union or Canada. 

Thank you for visiting SIKIDS.com, a Time Inc. site. Your and your children's privacy are important to us. This website contains areas for both adults and children to enjoy multi-purpose activities. Adults such as parents, guardians, and teachers may use this site to, among other things, order subscriptions and communicate with us. Children may enjoy educational features, fun games, and other activities. To better protect your and your children's privacy, we provide this policy explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by Time Inc. Refer to "Additional Information Regarding Children's Privacy" for an explanation of how we handle children's information.

|    
  
**The Information We Collect**  
Through Time Inc. publications, websites, and other media, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. You are able to visit much of this website and enjoy many Time Inc. publications and promotions without providing any personally identifiable information. Sometimes, however, we do need your personally identifiable information to provide you with the products and services that you request. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages and elsewhere include, but are not limited to: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. 

At some Time Inc. sites and through certain promotions, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online or offline and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. 

For certain promotions, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the promotion's activities and offerings. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. 

| back to top  
  
**How We Use and Share the Information**  
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us. 

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them. 

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "letter to our editors"), we may publish your name, screen name, and other information you have provided to us. 

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. 

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our publications and websites and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. 

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request. 

Agents and contractors of Time Inc. who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Time Inc.

We may transfer your personally identifiable information to other Time Inc. offices for internal management and administrative purposes. Your personal data will be transferred to other Time Inc. offices where necessary for the performance or conclusion of our contractual obligations to you or for your benefit. Transfers of personally identifiable information may also be made where necessary for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data. 

|    
  
**Privacy Options**  
If you prefer not to receive traditional mail or other off-line promotions from this or any other Time Inc. property or any companies not owned by Time Inc., please [click here](http://cgi.timeinc.net/cgi-bin/mail/dnp/privacy_centralized.cgi/sik?offline=yes&referring_url=&dnp_source=K). |    
  
If a Time Inc. site discloses personally identifiable information to companies not owned by Time Inc. who want to market products or services to you, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses. If you prefer not to receive online marketing information from companies not owned by Time Inc., please [click here](http://cgi.timeinc.net/cgi-bin/mail/dnp/privacy_centralized.cgi/sik?online=yes&referring_url=&dnp_source=K). 

Time Inc. may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive online marketing information from this or any other Time Inc. site, please [click here](http://cgi.timeinc.net/cgi-bin/mail/dnp/privacy_centralized.cgi/sik?online=yes&referring_url=&dnp_source=K). 

Time Inc. sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses. 

| back to top  
  
**Your California Privacy Rights: Notice to California Customers**  
California's "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the businesses' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. As discussed above, if you wish to opt-out of our sharing of your information with third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes offline please [click here](https://subscription.timeinc.com/storefront/privacy/sik/generic_privacy_form_offline.html?dnp-source=E), or for email please [click here](https://subscription.timeinc.com/storefront/privacy/sik/generic_privacy_form_online.html?dnp-source=E). To find out more about your opt-out rights, please contact us as described in the " **How to Contact Us**" section below.  |    
  
**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**  
Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

Time Inc. sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. Time Inc. has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information. 

Time Inc. sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. This privacy policy does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). For more information on the use of such third-parties, please [click here](http://subscription-assets.timeinc.com/prod/assets/themes/magazines/default/template-resources/html/legal/parties.html). 

|    
  
**Cookies**  
To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. 

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. 

We may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy. 

| back to top  
  
**Our Commitment to Security**  
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

|    
  
**How You Can Access or Correct Information**   
To inquire about personally identifiable information that this Time Inc. site has collected about you, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please email us by clicking [clicking here](mailto:consumeraffairs@customersvc.com).  |    
  
**Additional Information Regarding Children's Privacy**  
Your child's privacy is important to us, and we are committed to safeguarding children's personal information, and to helping parents and their children learn how to exercise control over personal information while exploring this website. Therefore, we have taken additional measures to tailor our content and offerings at our sites and portions of our sites directed to children under the age of 13, or which knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13, to help them protect their privacy while they use our sites. These measures include asking children to use non-personally identifiable screen names rather than their real names in certain activities and making efforts to prevent children from posting contact information. In addition, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in an activity. 

Visitors to the portions of our sites directed at children may participate in many of our offerings and activities without providing any personally identifiable information. To participate in certain of our interactive features, however, we may ask the user to provide us with the following types of information: first name, first initial of the last name, the visitor's e-mail address, parent's e-mail address, and age information. On some pages of our sites, such as where children can send postcards to their friends, we also may ask your child to provide information (e.g., friend's first name and e-mail address). We only use the personal information collected in these situations for the one-time purpose of responding to the request, and we delete the personal information from our systems after doing so. 

We use the information provided on our interactive pages for our internal purposes, to enable the user to enter one of our sweepstakes or contests, to express their opinions on various topics, to send electronic postcards to their friends, to otherwise participate in one of the activities on our site, or to respond to an e-mail message they have sent to us. We use information about others to enable the child to communicate with them or, in the case of the parent's e-mail address, to obtain your consent for participation in our activities (e.g., participation in a contest or subscription to SI Kids Magazine). We may also use information to enable parents and children to learn of additional product or service opportunities. We do not share children's personally identifiable information with outside third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy. Parents, if you would like to do any of the following, please send an e-mail to [customer service](mailto:consumeraffairs@customersvc.com) for instructions:  
    • access the personally identifiable information that this site has collected from your child,  
    • correct factual errors in such information,  
    • request to have this information deleted, or  
    • request that we no longer collect or maintain such information.

To protect your child's privacy and security online, we will take appropriate steps to help verify your identity before granting you access to the personal information that we collect and maintain about your child. 

|    
**Changes to This Policy**  
This Policy may be changed by Time Inc. The revised Policy will be posted to this page so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.  |    
|   
**How to Contact Us**  
Time Inc. is the operator of this website. If you have any questions or concerns about the Time Inc. Privacy Policy or its implementation please contact us via email by [clicking here](mailto:consumeraffairs@customersvc.com), call us at 800-318-1198 or write to us at the following address:

Time Customer Service  
Attention: Consumer Affairs - SIKIDS.com Privacy Policy  
3000 University Center Drive  
Tampa, Florida 33612-6408  
Telephone: 800-318-1198  
Email: [consumeraffairs@customersvc.com](mailto:consumeraffairs@customersvc.com)

| back to top  
|  This Privacy Policy was revised 5/13/13.
